(Leonard:)Great.
(Sheldon:)So I've decided
I'm going to collaborate with you.
(Leonard:)Great.
So, what exactly is it you do?
(Sheldon:)I know you chatter on about it all the time,
but I've never really paid attention.
(Leonard:)Right now, I'm designing an experiment
to study the soft component...
...of cosmic radiation at sea level,
but I don't need help.
(Sheldon:)Oh, sure you do.
(Sheldon:)Now see, what's this here in the schematic,
a laser array?
(Raj:)- Yes.
- Now, hmm...
(Sheldon:)What happens if you use argon lasers
instead of helium-neon?
- It would blow up.
- Are you sure?
- Pretty sure.
- "Pretty sure" is not very scientific.
Is this how you normally work?
Just hunches and guesses and stuff?
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Leonard:)I understand that you're going
through a bit of a career crisis.
(Leonard:)You're searching for some other area
where you can feel valuable and productive.
(Leonard:)But I need to tell you something,
and listen carefully.